{"questions":[{"question":"What is the disadvantage of the AGILE methodologies?","answers":["High software quality.","Less risks","Fragmented output ","Dividing the code into iterations?"],"Level":"1","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"What is Agile?","answers":["Iterative approach to project management.","Breakdown of project activities into linear sequential phases.","Each phase depends on the deliverables of the previous one and corresponds to a specialisation of tasks.","none of the above."],"Level":"1","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"Which of the requirements isn't functional requirement?","answers":["Operational Requirements.","Performance Requirements.","Data Requirements.","Interface Requirements."],"Level":"1","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"What are the missing requirements?","answers":["A requirement on a particular subject that is incomplete.","Requirements that are generally not described at all in the requirements document.","2 contradictory requirements in the content stated.","A requirement that describes functionality that has already been described in a document in one of the requirements"],"Level":"2","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"Whats the first step we should do before we start our project?","answers":["Requirements.","Development plan.","Contract review.","Quality plan."],"Level":"1","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"What is Verifiability in Review checks?","answers":["Is the requirement properly understood?","Is the origin of the requirement clearly stated?","Can the requirement be changed without a large impact on other requirements?","Is the requirement realistically testable?"],"Level":"3","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"What is the attribute that is not relevant to Waterfall from the given answers?","answers":["Poor quality.","Poor visibility.","Testing starts from day one.","Too risky."],"Level":"2","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Which from the answers isn't type of review?","answers":["Inspections for defect removal.","Reviews for progress assessment.","Review Leader.","Quality reviews."],"Level":"2","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Program testing is ____","answers":["an effeictive way to show absence of bugs.","is not effective to show presence of bugs.","can't assure absence of bugs.","none of the above."],"Level":"2","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"In black box testing we _____ .","answers":["know the software and test the actual code.","know the software and test functionality. ","don't know the software and test actual code.","don't know the software and test functionality."],"Level":"1","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"What is the type that is non relevant to maintaince from the given answers?","answers":["Corrective Maintenance.","Adaptive Maintenance.","logical maintenance.","Perfective Maintenance."],"Level":"2","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Maintenance costs affected by:","answers":["technical.","non-technical","1+2","non of the above."],"Level":"1","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"What is Software Architecture?","answers":["A software system\u2019s architecture is the set of principal design decisions about the system.","Software architecture is the blueprint for a software system\u2019s construction and evolution.","Design decisions encompass every facet of the system under development.","All the answers are correct."],"Level":"3","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"What is the step after the Software Architecture?","answers":["Requirements.","Implementation.","Low Level Design.",""],"Level":"2","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Who are the Females here","answers":["Sulafa","Sameh","Samya","Samer"],"Level":"1","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"Sulafa"},{"question":"Who ar1e the Females here","answers":["Sulafa","Sameh1","Samya","Samer"],"Level":"1","Team":"Giraffe","correct_ans":"Sulafa"}]}